Hi I'm Emily Larew, and we are working on our intermediate tap steps.
We're going to take a look at how to do a triple drawback.
So, remember if you looked previously at our double drawbacks, we just added another heel.
So this time we have three heels, okay.
So, knees bent, weight forward, we're going to do brush, heel, step, front, back, so that's your three heel sounds.
Brush, heel, step, front, back, one more time, brush, heel, step, front, back.
Again keep your body and your tap steps like right underneath your body, because otherwise it's going to be really hard to make it fast.
Brush, heel, step, front, back, brush, heel, step, front, back, brush, heel, step, front, back, brush, heel, step, front, back, da da da da da, alright.
So if we want to go ahead and add like a combination with our singles, doubles, and triples, we would do it like this.
And a one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, awesome.
Those were your single, double, and triple drawbacks all combined after you learn your triple drawback.